Kevin Tieu

Sacramento CA, 95823 916-216-1072 | kt216@humboldt.edu

PROFILE

A professional with 3 years of experience in retail serving customers by locating items throughout stores and providing the customer with a positive lasting impression as well as a years worth of warehouse experience in the means of production and shipment.

EDUCATION

Humboldt State University

2020-Present

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

California State University, Sacramento

Graduated 2014

- Bachelor of Arts in Political Science
- Pi Sigma Alpha Honor Society
- Dean's Honor List

EXPERIENCE

Golden State FC LLC

Sacramento, CA 2017-2019

Fulfillment Associate

- Technical proficiency in transport inventory and utilization of robotics service parcels efficiently and accurately.
- Collaboratively work with an interdisciplinary team to achieve safety and production standards.
- Knowledge to work in multiple departments including Inbound Stow, CAP, Vendor Returns, and Shipdock.
- Managing time effectively by supplying team members with empty totes and pallets.
- Teaching new associates the difference between master-packs and single case, pick error indicators, label and item mismatch, damaged items, and unscannable items.
- Trained in VCR, Jam Clearing, Picking, Counting, Tote Running, Stowing, Waterspidering, Shipdock, Pallet-Running, and Vendor Returns.

Wal-Mart

Elk Grove, CA

2015-2017

- Overnight Maintenace, Cap 2 Associate
 - Demonstrates dependability and reliability by being punctual, working assigned shifts, and completing responsibilities in a timely manner.
 - Talks with, listens to, or signals others to effectively exchange information; receives or gives direction; and effectively works as part of a team by responding to assistance requests throughout the facility.
 - Completes work assignments and priorities by using policies data and resources, collaborating with managers, co-workers, customers and other business partners, identifying priorities, deadlines and expectations.
 - Palletize items from truck into receiving and moving pallets with a pallet jack.
 - Training new associates current standards in cleaning and waxing floors, unloading and stacking boxes, organizing items into totes, and stocking shelves.